Visit Of Israeli Ambassador Guy Feldman & ZAKA’S Rabbi Yehuda Zahav To Prophet T.B. Joshua
Upon hearing of the support of Prophet T.B. Joshua to the nation of Israel the Israeli Ambassador to Nigeria
Guy Feldman visited Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Visit Of Israeli Ambassador Guy Feldman & ZAKA’S Rabbi Yehuda Zahav To Prophet T.B. Joshua
Israeli Ambassador Guy Feldman And Prophet T.B. Joshua
Israeli Ambassador Guy Feldman, Rabbi Yehuda Zahav & Prophet T.B. Joshua
Prophet T.B. Joshua's visit to the Holy Land - Jerusalem and the Sea of Galilee.
Prophet T.B. Joshua was invited to Israel to meet with important dignitaries, such as the Mayor of Jerusalem,
the Mayor of Tiberias,
Mayor of the Jordan Valley,
the deputy Mayor of Jerusalem,
the foreign affairs and media advisor to Mayor of Jerusalem.
Prophet T.B. Joshua’s Visit To The Holy Land
My name is Idan Grinbaum and I am the Mayor of the Jordan Valley Regional Council.
I appreciate it very much and it is a great honour to have Prophet T.B. Joshua near me.
I want to invite everybody to visit this beautiful place – the Sea of Galilee.
Join us here to see this beautiful and holy place; I will be expecting you.
I want to say, this is my great day being in the city of the Lord Jesus -
walking where He had walked during His earthly ministry.
I am honoured.
I am at home.
Thank you very much.
God will reward you.
You are our brother and special guest.
We are really honoured to have you here with us.
My name is Idan Grinbaum - keep watching Emmanuel TV.
How are you Prophet T.B. Joshua?
Welcome to our city – our Holy City.
Please come in.
Please, Sir.
Mayor Of Jerusalem Nir Barkat Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua At His Office In Jerusalem
Prophet Joshua, you give us a lot of honour.
Thank you.
The connection between you, Jerusalem and ZAKA is in many ways a connection of holiness
and this connection is very important to me.
Thank you very much.
I wanted to share that with you and thank you for your involvement and help.
I am at your honour and service.
I am very happy that you came by.
Thank you very much.
Anything, Yehuda, I can do to bond the relationship, anything I can do to help you, please tell my team.
I will maintain the relationship according to your mission and my mission.
Amen.
Thank you very much.
Mayor Of Jerusalem Nir Barkat Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua At His Office In Jerusalem
It is a great honour for us that you came here.
Thank you for taking your time.
I should come and tell you about Tiberias and the Sea of Galilee.
Mayor Of Tiberias Joseph Ben David Meets With Prophet T.B. Joshua In Tiberias Municipality
My name is Joseph Ben David, it’s actually, ‘Joseph son of David’. I am the Mayor of Tiberias.
Thank you.
Thank you, I am meeting my brother today.
Welcome!
Thank you very much.
I am more than excited to meet Prophet T.B. Joshua and his delegation.
Of course, I would like to take this opportunity to invite all the Emmanuel TV viewers
to come here to the Sea of Galilee.
See the blue area, here is the Sea of Galilee.
Come here to Tiberias in Israel!
We would like to host you and have you come to this beautiful land of miracles.
Keep watching Emmanuel TV!
Thank you.
Hi. I’m Gary Hull, a general manager of the newest radio station in Israel - “Voice Of Hope” for all the middle east.
We are so glad that God has opened His door to give us the place next to the beautiful Sea of Galilee,
where Jesus walked on the water, so that we bring the people the bread of life throughout all the middle east;
throughout Lebanon, through Syria and Jordan, and of course throughout the beautiful land of Galilee.
Our programs are being produced locally, and we are also going to be producing programs for other ministries
around the world, presenting the gospel of Jesus in the Arabic language to all who would listen.
We hope to encourage Christians who have lost their homes through sufferings and warfare.
We hope to encourage others who don't yet know the Lord to come to know the One who can save them
and give them eternal life.
Today we are so glad to be able to walk together with Prophet Joshua in the land of Jesus.
It is so good to know that he is continuing the broadcast the Word of God on Emmanuel TV.
Thank you for watching Emmanuel TV and stay tuned.
Be blessed.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Arrives At The Sea Of Galilee By Helicopter To Meet The Mayor Of Jordan Valley
An Israeli Television Station Awaits The Arrival Of Prophet T.B. Joshua To The Sea Of Galilee
Prophet T.B. Joshua Arrives At The Sea Of Galilee To Meet The Mayor Of Jordan Valley
Prophet!
Prophet Joshua! Hi. Thank you very much for coming to the Sea of Galilee.
Thank you Mayor.
I am happy to meet you.
I appreciate that you came all the way from Nigeria.
I heard so much about you.
Thank you very much. Let's go inside.
An Israeli Television Station Covers The Arrival Of Prophet T.B. Joshua To The Sea Of Galilee
Prophet T.B. Joshua Is Welcomed By The Mayor Of The Jordan Valley Regional Council
Please.
An Israeli TV Station Interviews Prophet T.B. Joshua As He Meets The Mayor Of Jordan Valley
Yes, exactly.
Pastor Joshua, may I ask, you are known as a Prophet; what is your prophecy for this land?
That’s why we are here.
Are we going to have war or peace?
No, don’t worry, that is why we are here.
We are here.
Whatever life brings, we will be here with you.
So, we are protected now?
By the grace of God.
Can you tell us in a few sentences, how did you get your power?
From my Father, Jesus, who was born in this land.
I am an inheritance of His grace – the grace of Jesus Christ.
What was your first prophecy?
It is not my prophecy; it is God’s prophecy.
You cure people by chasing the devil or demons out of them;
are demons here also in this land?
Demons are responsible for the pain, killing, stealing and destruction.
My purpose of praying for people is to give them relief,
to separate them from the demons that are responsible for the pain and affliction.
Mayor Of The Jordan Valley Idan Grinbaum Hosts Prophet T.B. Joshua At The Sea Of Galilee
Once again - thank you very much.
Prophet T.B. Joshua's visit to the Holy Land - Jerusalem and the Sea of Galilee.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Is Flown By Helicopter Over The Dead Sea To The Judean Desert
Prophet T.B. Joshua Arrives At Masada An Ancient Fortress And World Heritage Site In Southern Israel
Prophet T.B. Joshua Kneels To Pray
Prophet T.B. Joshua Visits Beit Gabriel At The Southern Tip Of The Sea Of Galilee